http://www.freedombankwv.com/index.cfm/privacy-policy

HomeProductsPersonalCheckingKasasa Cash CheckingKasasa Cash Back CheckingKasasa Tunes CheckingFree Kasasa SaverYour Choice CheckingSavingsKasasa SaverCDs & IRAsBusinessBusiness CheckingBusiness SavingsBusiness ServicesLendingPersonal LendingBusiness LendingServicesOnline BankingDebit/ATM CardsTelephone BankingFinancial CalculatorsRATESSecurityAlertsPrivacy PolicyUSA PATRIOT ActFunds AvailabilityAboutShareholder InformationInformational LinksContact
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We realize that our customers entrust us with personal information, and it is our policy to maintain our customers' information in a confidential manner. We are committed to protecting the security and privacy of our customers' personal information, as well as personal information of all consumers who visit our bank.
Information We Collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency
Protecting Children’s Privacy Online
We feel strongly about protecting the privacy of children.
As such, we do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under the age of 13, through the Bank’s web site, without obtaining verifiable consent from their parents and or legal guardian.
Should we determine that a child under the age of 13 sent or otherwise provided personal information to us, that information will be used only to obtain consent from their parent and or legal guardian.
Sharing Customer Information
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers to nonaffiliated third parties except as permitted by law.
Maintenance of Accurate Information
We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. Should you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about you, please notify us. We will investigate your concerns and correct any inaccuracies.
Sharing of Former Customer Information
We share and protect information about former customers the same way we share and protect information about current customers as described above.
Confidentiality and Security
We allow access to nonpublic personal information about you only to those employees who have a need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. Our employees are trained to respect customer privacy and to access customer information only when they have a business reason to know the information. In addition, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to safeguard your nonpublic information.
To access this website your Internet Explorer needs to be updated.
To get the best possible experience and added internet security using our website, we require you to upgrade your current web browser or install another web browser. A list of the most popular web browsers can be found below.
Just click on the icons to get to the download page.
Please note: These links will navigate you away from our domain.
We are not responsible for and have no control over the content or subject matter of these external links.
